ichro.me 2019-03-19

# iChrome - Privacy Policy

The column on the right provides a short summary of our privacy policy and is not legally binding.

**Last updated on: June 4th, 2017**

At iChrome, we collect and manage user data according to the following Privacy Policy. This document is part of our Terms of Service, and by using the iChrome website or using or installing any of iChrome’s browser extensions or other software (collectively, the “Services”), you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the [Terms of Service](https://ichro.me/tos). Please read the Terms of Service in their entirety and refer to them for definitions.

**If everyday language summaries are provided along with this Privacy Policy, they are for convenience only and are not legally binding.**

We collect and manage your data according to this privacy policy. 

These summaries aren't legally binding. 

## Information we collect

### Information you give us

When you create an account with us, we save certain information about you like your name, email address, gender, and photo so we can address you appropriately in the Services and in any communications and indicate to you which account you are logged in to the Services with, among other things.

When you are signed in and configure a widget or update your settings, that information is automatically saved. This could include, for example, your location that you entered to see a localized weather forecast or your news preferences.

When you create an account, you give us some personal information that we keep. We also save changes you make when signed in

### Information we automatically collect

We collect information about how you use the Services, like which widgets you use and how often you use the Services, to improve them. This information may be associated with your account or Internet Protocol (“IP”) address so we can track things like how many people use a particular widget instead of just how many times a widget was used.

This information is compiled into aggregate statistics that no single person can be identified from. After it’s compiled, we save the original information for a few days and then delete it. However, it may be stored indefinitely in our backups.

We collect info about how you use iChrome to improve it. Some of this is linked to your account, but we compile it into aggregate statistics and then delete it

### Information collected by or provided to third parties

We collect anonymous usage data using industry standard third party analytics services to monitor and better understand the performance and usage of the Services. The information we collect via third party services does not contain personal information, however it may include your IP address.

We use a user feedback and support service, UserVoice, to collect feedback and associate support requests with a particular user. Certain personally identifiable information, such as your name and email address, may be transmitted to UserVoice along with non-personally identifiable information like your IP address and how you submitted a support request, even before you make a support request. We use this information to better respond to support tickets by seeing more about you and how you use the Services along with your inquiry. Your usage of UserVoice, even from inside the Services, is governed by [UserVoice’s Terms of Service and Privacy Policy](http://ichrome.uservoice.com/tos).

We also use a web performance and security service, CloudFlare, to ensure that the Services are secure and operate quickly. CloudFlare may collect non personally identifiable information about you although we do not directly provide any information to them. Any such collection is governed by [CloudFlare’s Privacy Policy](https://www.cloudflare.com/security-policy/).

When you buy Pro or update your billing information some of your personally identifiable information is transmitted to Braintree along with your payment information. Your credit card information is never stored on our systems. Any information handling by Braintree is governed by [Braintree's policies](https://www.braintreepayments.com/legal).

We use Google Analytics to track general things, CloudFlare to make things faster and more secure, Braintree to process payments, and provide some data to UserVoice so we can handle feedback better

### Cookies

You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our systems may issue cookies when you use the Services.

We use cookies a little, but you can block them

## How we use the information we collect

We use the information we collect from you to deliver the Services to you and continuously enhance your user experience. Generally speaking, we use the collected information to communicate with you, fulfill your requests, and customize, operate, and improve the Services.

We may use your personal information to occasionally send you promotional information and updates regarding iChrome and its products and services.

The information that we collect from you may be used in aggregate form in various ways to optimize and improve the Services. While such information may be based on information about you, it will not identify you personally. We may use such information for the following purposes: website and application management, administration and security, promotional activities, and research and analysis.

We use the info we collect to make iChrome better and we might contact you occasionally

### Personal information

We may disclose your personal information without asking for your consent in order to protect the legal rights of iChrome or its affiliates, and each of their respective investors, directors, officers, employees, agents, and suppliers; to protect the safety and security of users of the Services or to enforce our Terms of Service; to protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; or to comply with or respond to the law or legal process or a request for cooperation by a government entity, whether or not legally required.

Also, in order to provide goods or services or to complete a transaction at your request, we may share your personal information with our third party service providers, including companies that assist with payment processing and other services.

We'll share your personal info for legal reasons and to complete transactions like Pro purchases

### Non-personal information and aggregate data

We may share with third parties your non-personal information and related aggregated data. For example, we may share IP addresses of our users to provide anonymous aggregated data to business partners about the volume of use on the Services and the specific parts of the Services in which users are most interested. Because this form of data does not identify particular users, these third parties will not be able to contact you based solely on this data.

We might share analytics information and statistics with third parties, but data like that doesn't include anything personal

### Change of control

If we sell all or part of our business, or make a sale or transfer of assets, or are otherwise involved in a merger or business transfer, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy, we may transfer your personal information and non-personal information to one or more third parties as part of such a transaction.

If iChrome is sold, we may transfer your information. 

## Consent to transfer information

We are based in the United States and the information we collect is governed by U.S. law. By accessing or using the Services or otherwise providing information to us, you consent to the processing and transfer of information in and to the U.S. and other countries.

We're in the U.S., so your info comes here

## Changes to this privacy policy

We may change this privacy policy from time to time at our sole discretion. If we make any changes, we will notify you of such changes by posting the updated privacy policy on the iChrome website. We encourage you to check this page frequently for any changes. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. Your continued use of the Services after any such changes have been posted will constitute your acceptance of them.

If we update this policy, we'll post the changes here

## Contact information

Should you have any questions about this privacy policy or our terms and conditions, please email us at support@ichro.me.

If you have questions, email us at support@ichro.me
